Rawy Murgany

+201014268239 | rawymo@outlook.com | Sidi Bishr, Alexandria, Egypt

Summary

A self-taught, full-stack web developer specializing in both front end and back end, building responsive and scalable web apps from concept to deployment since June 2021. Also a self-taught computer maintenance technician since 2015 and a cellular telephone maintenance technician since 2012.

You will see gaps and sudden career changes in my CV, most of them are because I'm a refugee in Egypt and I'm facing lots of barriers and obstacles, but the bright side is that they gave me diverse experiences. I'll be happy to explain them if needed. Thank you for reading. Looking forward to hearing from you soon.

Experience

Full Stack Web Developer - Django developer - Web developer | 06/2021 - Present | Freelancer | Alexandria, Egypt

- Full stack web development. React-Diango or HTML-Diango.
- Writing codes to build websites (full stack) from concept to production based on custom designs.
- Database designing and programming with Python and Django.
- · Working with databases like PostgreSQL, MySQL and SQLite3.
- Data serialization (REST APIs) with Django REST Framework.
- Building responsive, user-friendly and scalable websites with React JS, JQuery, HTML, CSS, bootstrap and JavaScript and Django.
- API programming with Python and Django.
- API integration (back end / front end).
- · Site animations with CSS, JQuery and JavaScript.
- · Code Debugging and testing.
- · Continuously learning new work-related skills as the demand arise.

Training & Quality Control Manager/Administrative assistant | 07/2021 - 03/2022 | Section F (Chain of 3 Restaurants) | Alexandria, Egypt

- Managed the training and orientation of new employees, overseeing their work.
- Collected customer feed back, resolved customer complaints and maintained contact lists.
- Coordinated between the different departments of management and the three branches of the restaurant.
- Prepared and organized meetings and appointments.
- Took minutes of meetings, analyzed the outcome and prepared list of actions in coordination with the relevant departments and the CEO.
- · Assisted in the preparation of regularly scheduled reports.
- · Ordered office supplies.
- Provided general support to visitors.
- · Covered the reception desk when required.
- Maintained computer and manual filing systems.
- Replied to emails, telephones and face to face inquiries.
- Coordinated repairs to office and restaurant equipment
- · Greeted and assisted visitors to the office.
- Carried out administrative duties such as filing, typing, copying, binding, scanning, etc.
- · Conducted data entry.
- · Any other task given by management.

Cellular Telephone & Computer Technician - Business Owner | 08/2017 - 07/2019 | Samara Phones | Cairo, Egypt

- Consulting with customers to understand the problems they're facing with their phones or computers.
- Diagnosing and troubleshooting cell phones and computers to identify hardware or software problems.
- Disassembling and assembling all types of phones and computers for the purpose of repair.
- Updating, installing and configuring hardware, software and drivers to maximize system functionality.
- Fixing hardware problems and/or changing faulty parts like charging ports, mics, speakers, earpiece, screens, etc.

- Accessory sales.
- Selling phone accessories and computer accessories.
- · Managing one staff.

Cellphone maintenance technician - shop owner | 08/2012 - 10/2016 | Albalouly Phones | Khartoum, Sudan

- · Consulting with customers to understand the problems they're facing with their devices.
- Diagnosing and troubleshooting cell phones to identify hardware or software issues.
- Disassembling and assembling all types of phones for the purpose of repair.
- Updating, installing and configuring hardware, software and drivers to maximize system functionality.
- Fixing hardware problems and/or changing faulty parts like charging ports, mics, speakers, earpiece, screens, etc.
- · Accessory sales.
- Customer Service.

Production Supervisor / Administrative Assistance | 01/2010 - 12/2012 | Awaad Advertisement Company | Khartoum , Sudan

- Working with a team of welders, fitters and a graphic designer, I oversaw the production of advertisement sign posts and billboards from sourcing for materials to installation of finished products, supervising 5 employees.
- Coordinating between the different departments to ensure smooth and timely delivery of projects.
- Meeting and consulting with customers and taking specifications for their desired design of signs and/or boards.
- Briefing team members on new projects and the tasks to be taken.
- Ensured finished products meet or exceed customer expectation.
- · Handled multiple projects.
- Ensured operation of equipment by completing preventive maintenance requirements, calling for repairs, maintaining equipment inventories, evaluating new equipment and techniques.
- Maintained supplies inventory by checking stock to determine inventory level, anticipating needed supplies, placing and expediting orders for supplies and verifying receipt of supplies.
- Carried out administrative duties such as filing, typing, copying, binding, scanning, etc.
- · Covered the reception desk when required.
- Maintained computer and manual filing systems.
- Greeted and assisted visitors to the office / workshop.
- Any other responsibility given by management.

Technical Skills

Django. React.js. PostgreSQL. MySQL. jQuery. AJAX. I18n. Python (Programming Language). Cascading Style Sheets (CSS). HTML5. Bootstrap. JavaScript. REST APIs. Technical Support. Front-End Development. Back-End Web Development. Django REST Framework. Full-Stack Development.

Soft Skills

Small Business Management, Time management, Communication skills, Continuous Improvement, Customer Service, Creative Problem Solving, Analytical Skills, Attention to Detail, Consulting

Education

Secondary School / High School | Meridi Center for the Displaced.- Comboni College | 05/2009 | Khartoum, Sudan Grade 72%

Certificates

Data Collection and Processing with Python-U of Michigan, Python Fuctions Files and Dictionaries - U of Michigan, Python Basics - University of Michigan | Coursera, HTML - SoloLearn